Guide to NYU Publications: Preservation Copies 1832-1994 RG 1.0
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1956 (Box 85, Item 5)
  - Education Violet, 1958 (Box 85, Item 6)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1958 (Box 86, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254295
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1959 (Box 86, Item 2)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1960 (Box 86, Item 3)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1962 (Box 86, Item 4)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1963 (Box 86, Item 5)
  - Education Violet, 1963 (Box 87, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254303
  - Education Violet, 1964 (Box 87, Item 2)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1965 (Box 87, Item 3)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1966 (Box 87, Item 4)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1967 (Box 87, Item 5)
  - Education Violet, 1968 (Box 87, Item 6)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1969 (Box 87, Item 7)
  - Education Violet, 1970 (Box 87, Item 8)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1971 (Box 87, Item 9)
  - Commerce Violet, 1923 (Box 88, Item 1)
    barcode #: 3 1142 042254311
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1926 (Box 88, Item 2)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254311
  - Commerce Violet, 1929 (Box 88, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet, 1931 (Box 88, Item 4)
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1934 (Box 88, Item 5)
  - Commerce Violet, 1936 (Box 88, Item 6)
  - Commerce Violet, 1938 (Box 88, Item 7)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1972 (Box 89, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254329
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1973 (Box 89, Item 2)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1974 (Box 89, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet, 1913 (Box 89, Item 4)
  - Commerce Violet (3 copies), 1917 (Box 89, Item 5)
  - Commerce Violet, 1918 (Box 89, Item 6)
  - Commerce Violet, 1921 (Box 89, Item 7)
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1922 (Box 89, Item 8)
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1961 (Box 90, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254337
  - Commerce Violet (3 copies), 1962 (Box 90, Item 2)
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1963 (Box 90, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1964 (Box 90, Item 4)
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1940 (Box 91, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254345
  - Commerce Violet, 1944 (Box 91, Item 2)
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1950 (Box 91, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet (2 copies), 1951 (Box 91, Item 4)
  - Commerce Violet (3 copies), 1969 (Box 92, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254352
  - Commerce Violet, 1978 (Box 92, Item 2)
  - The Violet, 1931 (Box 92, Item 3)
  - The Violet, 1933 (Box 92, Item 4)
  - The Violet, 1938 (Box 92, Item 5)
  - The Violet, 1939 (Box 92, Item 6)
  - The Violet (2 copies), 1940 (Box 92, Item 7)
  - The Violet (2 copies), 1941 (Box 92, Item 8)
  - The Violet, 1942 (Box 92, Item 9)
  - The Album, 1929 (Box 92, Item 10)
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1953 (Box 93, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254360
  - Commerce Violet, 1954 (Box 93, Item 2)
  - Commerce Violet (3 copies), 1955 (Box 93, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1966 (Box 94, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254378
  - Commerce Violet (4 copies), 1967 (Box 94, Item 2)
  - Commerce Violet, 1968 (Box 94, Item 3)
  - Commerce Violet, 1969 (Box 94, Item 4)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1977 (Box 95, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254386
  - The Album (3 copies), 1978 (Box 95, Item 2)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1981 (Box 95, Item 3)
  - The Album (5 copies), 1982 (Box 95, Item 4)
  - The Album (5 copies), 1983 (Box 95, Item 5)
  - Bellevue Violet, 1925-1943 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225722 3
  - Education Violet, 1931-1949 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Torch, 1981-1988 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225723 1
  - Torch, 1989-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225724 9
  - Dental Violet, 1926-1943 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225725 6
  - Violet, 1891-1913 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225726 4
  - Violet, 1891-1913 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225727 2
  - Violet, 1928-1937 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225728 0
  - Violet, 1928-1937 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225729 8
  - Violet, 1948-1959 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225730 6
  - Album, 1927-1936 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Album, 1938-1949 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225731 4
  - Torch, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Commerce Violet, 1913-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225732 2
  - Commerce Violet, 1938-1949 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225733 0
  - Dental Violet, 1943-1949 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225734 8
  - Alumnus, 1921-1932 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225735 5
  - Alumnus, 1932-1938 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225736 3
  - Alumni Catalog, 1833-1905 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - General Alumni Catalog, 1916 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - NYU Glee Club Bulletins, 1938-1952 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Violet, 1915 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225737 1
  - Violet, 1921-1923 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Violet, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Violet, 1940 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Violet, 1942 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Violet, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Violet, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Violet, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Violet, 1898 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225658 9
  - Violet, 1921 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Violet, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Violet, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Violet, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1944 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1946 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1947 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Violet, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Torch, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Violet, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225659 7
  - Violet, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1955 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1956 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Violet, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Violet, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Violet, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Violet, 1963-1965 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225660 5
  - Violet, 1967-1970 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1971 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Violet, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Torch, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Torch, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Violet, 1897 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225661 3
  - Violet, 1907 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Violet, 1909-1910 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Violet, 1918 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Violet, 1922 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1925 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Violet, 1924 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Violet, 1930 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Violet, 1932 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Violet, 1935 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1945 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04225634 0
  - Violet, 1961-1965 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Violet, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1970 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Torch, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1973 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Torch, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Education Violet, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Education Violet, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1953 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Education Violet, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Education Violet, 1958 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Education Violet, 1959 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Education Violet, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Education Violet, 1963 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Education Violet, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Dental Violet, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Dental Violet, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Commerce Violet, 1951 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Commerce Violet, 1952 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Commerce Violet, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Education Violet, 1954 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Education Violet, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Education Violet, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Education Violet, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Education Violet, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Medicine Violet, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Medicine Violet, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Medicine Violet, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Medicine Violet, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Medicine Violet, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Alumni News, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Alumni News, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Alumni News, 1976 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Alumni News, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Alummi News, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Alumni News, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Alumni News, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Alumni News, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Torch (2 copies), 1981 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Torch (3 copies), 1982 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Torch (3 copies), 1986 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Violet (9 copies), 1990 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Violet (15 copies), 1990 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Violet (15 copies), 1990 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Violet (15 copies), 1990 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Violet (15 copies), 1990 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1990 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Torch (9 copies), 1991 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Torch (7 copies), 1993 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Torch (20 copies), 1993 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Torch, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Torch (16 copies), 1994 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1994 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Torch, 1995 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Torch (20 copies), 1995 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Torch (10 copies), 1998 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Torch (8 copies), 1995 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1998 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Torch (16 copies), 1998 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Torch (11 copies), 1998 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Torch (4 copies), 1999 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 138, File 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1999 (Box 140, File 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Torch (6 copies), 1998 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Torch (9 copies), 1999 (Box 142, File 2)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1998 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1998 (Box 144, File 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 1998 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Torch (17 copies), 2001 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Torch (17 copies), 2001 (Box 147, File 1)
  - Torch (9 copies), 2001 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Torch (7 copies), 2002 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Torch (2 copies), 2002 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Torch (15 copies), 2003 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Torch (16 copies), 2003 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Torch, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Torch (10 copies), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Torch (3 copies), 2005 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Torch (10 copies), 2003 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Torch (6 copies), 2005 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Torch (17 copies), 2005 (Box 153, File 1)
  - Torch (18 copies), 2005 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Torch (17 copies), 2005 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Torch supplement (50 copies), 2001 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Torch Supplement (5 copies), 2002 (Box 156, File 2)
  - Torch supplement (39 copies), 2003 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Torch (10 copies), 2005 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 158, File 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Violet (17 copies), 1990 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Torch (19 copies), 1993 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Violet, 1990 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Torch (6 copies), 1998 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Torch (5 copies), 1995 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Torch (7 copies), 1993 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Torch (11 copies), 2004 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Stern, 2003 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Torch, 2000 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Torch (2 copies), 1998 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1908-1909 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04227271 9
  - New York University Catalogue, 1911-1912 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1915-1916 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1916-1917 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1919-1920 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1920-1921 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1922-1923 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1923-1924 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1924-1925 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1925-1926 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1926-1927 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1928-1929 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1929-1930 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Joseph I. Lubin Memorial Lectures: "The Dollar, Debt, and the Deficit", Anthony M. Solomon (4 copies), 1987 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Joseph I. Lubin Memorial Lectures: "Effective Leadership in a Competitive World", Frederick D.S. Choi (10 copies), 1998 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - Joseph I. Lubin Memorial Lectures: "Contemporary Issues in the American Economy", Daniel E. Diamond (4 copies), 1992 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Joseph I. Lubin Memorial Lectures: "Contemporary Challenges: American Business in a Global Economy", Daniel E. Diamond (3 copies), 1995 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - Stern, 2002 (Box 170, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04688445 1
  - Stern, 2003 (Box 170, Item 2)
  - Stern, 2004 (Box 170, Item 3)
  - Stern (2 copies), 2005 (Box 170, Item 4)
  - Stern (2 copies), 2006 (Box 170, Item 5)
  - Stern (3 copies), 2007 (Box 170, Item 6)
  - Stern, 2009 (Box 170, Item 7)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1891 (Box 171, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 04688446 9
  - Violet, 1892 (Box 171, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1893 (Box 171, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1894 (Box 171, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1895 (Box 171, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1896 (Box 171, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1897 (Box 171, Item 7)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1898 (Box 171, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1900 (Box 171, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1901 (Box 171, Item 10)
  - Violet, 1902 (Box 171, Item 11)
  - Stern (10 copies), 2000 (Box 172, Item 1)
  - Stern (2 Copies), 2002 (Box 172, Item 2)
  - Stern, 1982 (Box 173, Item 1)
  - Stern (2 Copies), 1987 (Box 173, Item 2)
  - Stern (2 Copies), 1988 (Box 173, Item 3)
  - Stern, 1991 (Box 173, Item 4)
  - Stern (2 Copies), 1994 (Box 173, Item 5)
  - Stern, 1995 (Box 173, Item 6)
  - Stern (6 Copies), 1999 (Box 173, Item 7)